{
    id: "0",
    question: "Which of the following data connectivity options is the best to use when both availability and reliability is required?",
    options: [
        "Wifi",
        "Blueteeth",
        "Wired",
        "Cellular"
    ],
    correct: "Wired",
},
{
    id: "2",
    question: "To reduce the risk of installing unapproved or possibly malicious software on a smartphone, a user should ...",
    options: [
        "download apps from a user-friendly community",
        "update the firmware before downloading any app from anywhere",
        "utilize the vendor-provided app store",
    ],
    correct: "utilize the vendor-provided app store",
},
{
    id: "3",
    question: "When trying to activate the operating system, a user receives a notice that the software is not genuine. Which of the following security threats has occurred?",
    options: [
        "phishing",
        "license theft",
        "virus attack",
    ],
    correct: "license theft",
},
{
    id:"4",
    question:"Which of the following tool is used for Wi-Fi hacking?",
    options: [
        "Nessus",
        "Snort",
        "Aircrack-ng",
        "Wireshark",
    ],
    correct:"Aircrack-ng",
},
{
    id:"5",
    question:"Which of the following is an example of physical data leakage?",
    options: [
        "Phishing",
        "Dumpster diving",
        "Printers and photocopies",
    ],
    correct:"Phishing",
},
{
    id:"6",
    question:"Which of the following is th most important activity in your system hacking?",
    options: [
        "Information Gathering",
        "Cracking passwords",
        "Covering tracks",
    ],
    correct:"hacking passwords",
},
{
    id:"7",
    question:"We should turn a ____ on to protect our computer from hacker(s).",
    options: [
        "Script",
        "Firewall",
        "Antivirus",
    ],
    correct:"Firewall",
},
{
    id:"8",
    question:"Which of the following is an example of a fishing attack?",
    options: [
        "Sending someone an email that contains a malicious link that is disguised to look like an email from someone the person knows",
        "Creating a fake website that looks nearly identical to a real website in order to trick users into entering their login information",
        "Sending someone a text message that contains a malicious link that is disguised to look like a notification that the person has won a contest",
        "All of the above"
    ],
    correct:"All of the above",
},
{
    id:"9",
    question:"A group of computers that is networked together and used by hackers to steal information is called a ___",
    options: [
        "Operating System",
        "DDoS",
        "Rootkit",
        "Botnet",
    ],
    correct:"Botnet",
},
{
    id:"10",
    question:"Which of the following four passwords is the most secure?",
    options: [
        "Dog123",
        "123456",
        "T33ddYB34R4L1f3!!!",
        "into!89",
    ],
    correct:"T33ddYB34R4L1f3!!!",
},
{
    id:"11",
    question:"If a public Wi-Fi network (such as in an airport or caf√©) requires a password to access, is it generally safe to use that network for sensitive activities such as online banking?",
    options: [
        "Yes",
        "No",
    ],
    correct:"No",
},
{
    id:"12",
    question:"What kind of cybersecurity risks can be minimized by using a Virtual Private Network (VPN)?",
    options: [
        "Key-Logging",
        "Phishing Attacks",
        "Use of insecure Wifi networks",
    ],
    correct:"Use of insecure Wifi networks",
},
{
    id:"13",
    question:"A website sending you a code to your mobile device before you log in is an example of...",
    options: [
        "Antivirus Protection",
        "Password Encryption",
        "Two Factor identification",
    ],
    correct:"Two Factor identification",
},
{
    id:"14",
    question:"State whether True or False: Data encryption is used to ensure confidentiality.",
    options: [
        "True",
        "False",
    ],
    correct:"True",
},
{
    id:"15",
    question:"Which of the following statements concerning the firewall is true? ",
    options: [
        "It is a barrier created to stop files from hurting the company.", 
        "It is a tool put in place at a business's perimeter to stop uninvited physical entrance.", 
        "It is a device placed at an organisation's perimeter to prevent unwanted access.",
    ],
    correct:" It is a device placed at an organisation's perimeter to prevent unwanted access.",
},